<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asish Kumar - Student in India</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Asish Kumar - Student in India</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2024, Asish Kumar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hindi Translation of Cantor and KDE Connect - SoK 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/cantor-kdeconnect-hindi-translation-sok-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/cantor-kdeconnect-hindi-translation-sok-2024/</guid>
      <description>Hindi Translation of Cantor and KDE connect - Season of KDE 2024 This is the second and last blog for SoK 2024.&#xA;During the second half of Season of KDE, I translated Cantor and KDE connect in hindi. Cantor and KDE connect had about 1000 and 500 lines respectively.&#xA;In order to translate these softwares, I took reference from google translate and AI models to improve on my translation. Translation memory did a great job in finding duplicates and helped me to avoid translating the same words again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hindi Translation of Merkuro - SoK 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/merkuro-hindi-translation-sok-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/merkuro-hindi-translation-sok-2024/</guid>
      <description>Hindi Translation of Merkuro - Season of KDE 2024 In this blog, I will discuss my experience with season of KDE 2024.&#xA;I came to know about this program through a youtube video. I was given some pre tasks to complete by the mentors of the project which can be found at https://github.com/officialasishkumar/translation-kde-applications.&#xA;After completing the pre-tasks, I applied for the project and eventually got selected.&#xA;During my SoK period, I have to translate Merkuro, KDE connect, KTorrent and Cantor in Hindi.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
